MATTHEW HOBBS-HURRELL

matthewhobbshurrell@icloud.com • 07481490631 • Ipswich, Suffolk



Summary

A focused and methodical problem solver with a keen eye for details and a strong work ethic. Entrepreneurial and creative mindset with experience in all aspects of company and self-management. Highly driven and determined to succeed in personal and professional goals.





Technical Skillset













Portfolio Projects

Movie Soundtrack Quiz - An interactive online quiz where a user can test their soundtrack knowledge. Technologies used - Vanilla HTML, CSS, JavaScript, GitHub, Git, GitPod and Slack. Live Deployment | GitHub Repo

Labyrinth of Riddles - A puzzle-based word game that a user can interact with via terminal commands. Technologies used - Vanilla Python, Git, GitHub, GitPod, Heroku, Slack and draw.io. Live Deployment | GitHub Repo

Disney Food Guide - An online guide of the top-rated food, drinks and restaurants at Disney World. Technologies Used - Vanilla HTML, CSS, Git, GitHub, GitPod, Balsamiq and Slack. Live Deployment | GitHub Repo

Collaborative Projects

DBAA - A social networking and events platform for the LGBTQ+ community. Created for the Code Institute Pride Hackathon.

Technologies Used - HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, Django, GitHub, Heroku, Git and GitPod. Live Deployment | GitHub Repo

Education



Higher National Diploma (HND) Full Stack Software Development

Code Institute | Online May 2022 - May 2023 Currently Enrolled



Intermediate Level Apprenticeship Business Skills and Administration

Federation for Industry Sector Skills & Standards | Ipswich 2014



Certificate of Higher Education Music

Colchester Institute | Colchester 2012



BTEC National Diploma Music

Suffolk New College | Ipswich

Graduated with Triple Distinction



GCSEs General Studies

Stowmarket High School | Stowmarket

Maths - A, English Literature - A English - B, Science Double Award - B B History - B, Music - B, ICT - Pass

Professional Experience

Company Director & Founder

One Stop Inventories Ltd Ipswich, Suffolk 06/2020 - Current

Professional Musician

Self Employed Worldwide, International 06/2017 - 03/2020

Inventory Clerk

Haart Estate Agents Ipswich, Suffolk 03/2012 - 06/2017

- Provided market leading inventory services to lettings agents and private landlords
- Developed and implemented marketing strategies
- Designed and refined innovative procedures and protocols
- Actively recruited and oversaw training for staff
- Maintained website and social media
- Controlled and updated databases
- Calculated monthly figures and accounts
- Organised diaries for staff
- Implemented staff payroll
- Successfully expanded market share across Suffolk and Essex
- Actualised strategies to continually improve services
- Generated steady and sustained profit
- Entertained audiences internationally across Asia and Europe in luxury hotels and on cruise ships
- Continually updated and expanded repertoire
- Organised and coordinated regular daily rehearsals and practice sessions
- Maintained website and social media
- Analysed audience demographic to tailer and deliver engaging and entertaining performances
- Developed extensive knowledge of live sound equipment and the latest software
- Resident inventory clerk for the UK's largest independent estate agent
- Provided inventory services to private landlords
- Attended property inspections and produced comprehensive written reports detailing property condition and damages
- Spearheaded implementation of innovative new inventory software
- Organised diary and databases
- Oversaw the workload of seven branches throughout Suffolk and Essex
- Trained and mentored new staff

Certifications

June 2022 Hackathon: 2nd Place

Code Institute | Show Certificate

Build Responsive Real World Websites With HTML5 and CSS3

Jonas Schmedtmann - Udemy | Show Certificate

5-Day Coding Challenge

Code Institute | Show Certificate

Soft Skills

- Exceptional attention to detail
- Experience in all areas of running a business
- Entrepreneurial and creative mindset
- Strong administration skills
- Strategy creation and implementation experience
- Eagerness and enthusiasm to continue learning
- Excellent communication skills
- Computer proficiency
- Management experience
- Organised and methodical
- Highly focused
- Innovative problem solver